

kulsha_85@mail.ru +375 29 5678601 site: vitalikulsha.github.io

Junior Java Developer

Belarus, Zhodino

Skype: vitali kulsha Linkedin: vitali-kulsha Github: vitalikulsha VK: vitali kulsha

I work as a leading process engineer. Extensive experience in design and 3D modeling (KOMPAS, SolidWorks, Inventor, ProEngineer). I am developing in JAVA development. Completed the Java Basics Upskill online course at EPAM, as well as various webinars, marathons and free courses.

Hard skills Java SE/EE Maven SOL

Hibernate Spring HTML **REST** Servlet/JSP IntelliJ IDEA Junit **CSS** MVC **JDBC** JS Git

Foreign languages

English — Elementary (Beginner)

Education

BNTU | MEF

«Tool production technology» Higher education | 09.2005 - 06.2011

Courses

Java Guru | Online | 02/21 - 03/21

Course "RPA (telegram bot)"

ITEA | Online | 09/21 - 09/21

Corse "HTML-marathon"

EPAM | Online | 11/20 - 03/21 Course "Java Basics"

EPAM | Online | 03/21 - 05/22 Course "Java Basics Upskill Lab"

ITVDN | Online | 07/21 - 09/21 Course "Java Developer"

Certificates:

Java Starter

Java EE Basics

JDBC & Hibernate

Git Basics

Spring

Spring Data

STEPIK | Online | 05/22 - H.B.

Certificates:

SQL

WEB technologies

Java web service part 1

Java web service part 2

Work experience

Leading Process Engineer

CJSC Belgee | Borisov district

08.2020 - until now

Ensuring the technology and quality of production of bodies in the welding workshop

Workshop foreman

CJSC Belgee | Borisov district

07.2016 - 08.2020

Personnel management, support for the production of bodies in the welding workshop

Process Engineer

LLC Belavtozapchast | Zhodino

02.2015 - 07.2016

Hydraulic cylinder production technology

Design engineer

LLC Snackpro | Smolevichi district

05.2013 - 01.2015

Design of units and mechanisms for the food industry

Design engineer

LLC Belavtozapchast | Zhodino

10.2010 - 05.2012

Construction of special devices and hydraulic cylinders

Projects

REST API Application

«Library» app using Spring Boot and REST API with ability to change authors and categories.

https://github.com/vitalikulsha/UpSkill Lab1 JavaBasics/tree/ master/WebBasicsREST

Java web project using servlets and JSP

"Library" system with the ability to search and order books.

https://github.com/vitalikulsha/JavaWebProject

Console Application

Console application for creating/editing/viewing users and saving to a file. Without the use of third-party libraries and frame-

https://github.com/vitalikulsha/user-catalog

Telegram bot

Telegram bot in the form of a quiz

https://github.com/vitalikulsha/BLRweAreOne bot

Soft skills

- Sociability
- A responsibility
- Quick learning
- Tenacity
- Organization
- Initiative